when life takes an unexpected turn how
do you find the strength to keep going
listen to real life stories of
resilience and determination and how
these experiences change lives for the
better I'm an a daughter a mother and a
manual life policy owner since 2009 and
these are the stories of Ivon and
Marielle my mother had a lot of Health
complications and then so in the middle
of med school I found myself in the ER
with her and then one month in the ICU
so I had to stop schooling for a while
and so one day we received an envelope
it was from uh Manu life and the money
we received from those three policies
was enough to um help pay for the
medical expenses and enable me to
continue um
medicine what about you misson I lost my
husband when I was 30 years old so
financially and then you'll have to go
ahead and deal P emotionally and then
raising the kid on your own now that
she's in college she's currently taken
up nursing the funds that we're getting
from uh the insurance is really helpful
knowing medical field is actually very
it's very expensive expensive that's
probably how I will honor him um to make
sure that our daughter is also prepared
in the future I'm also happy that I
decided to pursue medicine it's actually
very fun and I'm very rewarding because
I'm practicing where my mother was born
so it's another added layer of like I'm
connected to her I do feel her presence
and I do feel she's happy
[Music]